Feels like pressure
My days, it came unsteady
Pulled the truth up from below
Everything I didn't wanna know
Not who I was, but what I hid
All the things I never handled, never did
Every habit, every crack
This isn't power over analysis, God
Every boundary left unspoken
I called it love called free, but freedom
Without structure breaks and open
What it takes to be was something to guide
But every signal that I display
came a pattern others could play so now i feel weighs inside not closed in control not every
truth needs to be told because it's god serves your time and doesn't mean stop oppression it's
choosing time impression you don't not greasy i just got out of the bath yeah but there's a
couple there's some cool nightbok events actually this is gonna be an open panel night like i
put open panel in the title so maybe that will bring some new people who knows or anybody that
Come on up. Hi, baby
It's Rudy. Some people just came for the song. I like that.
They like when I come on, but they like the song. Well, I think you were coming anyway.
Hi, Rude.
Hi, Rude. We'll start another. Hey, what's up?
Well, yeah.
Well, I wait for people to come in and if you want to join the panel, the link's up there.
Right back.
Casting from the dark to the weird ones the souls they tried to write or the transmissions activated
We were saying no didn't know the signal
Tell that it disappeared swallowed by the algorithm the ghost in the machine, but they forgot something
Some men don't enter the room to be seen
Change the temporary on decay
It's in digital range. Error card spread like maps reading loss
webcando
internet outcast
roundtroll pings
let all shake down
the psychic sits still
with dangerous grin
watching every move
before the game begins
everybody's screaming
attention online
selling fake copy
better time
but silence cuts deeper
than noise ever can
philosopher
with static in his plans
he don't chase the spotlight
as the throne
second he goes home
she was a 333
digital priest
discarding the frequency
while psyches
studies human nature
like a hacker
Need for fake aggression, notice people in the-
Chase the spot like a weapon, turn in as the throne
The algorithm can't contain here, the signal found its own
This world rewards noise, but noise burns out
That's where the real power, not in screaming, will to predict
Started with somebody refusing to crawl, kill hesitation slowly
Let strategy take form, because calm becomes when it survives
In the static path, an empty flame A man became movement and avatar